gaywatch.com 2009-03-27

# Gaywatch - Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

FOR [WWW.GAYWATCH.COM](http://www.gaywatch.com/)

THIS POLICY WAS LAST UPDATED ON JANUARY 1, 2006

PLEASE READ THIS CAREULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE.

**Privacy Policy**

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how Gaywatch.com treats your personal information, including any information related to your use of Gaywatch.com services.� Personal information includes your name, address, email address or phone number, and consists of information that is not otherwise publicly available.

**Information Collection and Use**

Gaywatch.com collects personal information when you register, such as your email address, zip code and age.� For full memberships and some possible future services we may also collect your full name, address, phone number and credit card information.� Once you register with Gaywatch.com and sign in to our services you are not completely anonymous to us.� Gaywatch.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address.� Gaywatch.com uses the information you provide to fulfill your requests or services.� We also reserve the right to share personal information, such as your name, address, telephone number, age, and email address with our advertisers, sponsors, or other third parties.� Your billing information such as credit/debit card or bank account information is never sold, distributed, or shared with any external enterprise, business or individual.� 

We also use your identifying information such as e-mail address and other data to clarify information you may have listed, to notify you about Gaywatch.com information and updates, and to offer you memberships and services.

We may use information about you and other users to improve our marketing and promotion, to improve editorial content, and to help us figure out our community�s needs.

Gaywatch.com may set and access Gaywatch.com session cookies on your computer.� 

**Children**

When a child under the age of 18 attempts to register with Gaywatch.com and provides truthful profile information, they are denied access.� 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Gaywatch.com may update this policy.� We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Gaywatch.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
